Tang Thien An

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam



tangthienan9@gmail.com



0963893893



linkedin.com/in/tang-thien-an-0691a4195

Summary

I've worked for more than 2 years as a Front-end ReactJs developer and I love it. On the other hand, I have the ability to catch up with new technology quite fast.

The thing that let me work well is people, it would be wonderful if my teammate could help me develop myself in both technical and life.

Experience



Software Engineer

NAB Innovation Centre Vietnam

Dec 2021 - Present (1 year 9 months)

For full-time official work, my team collaborated with Australian and Indian teams. My squad takes responsibility for a mini-app. My role is to implement the UI within integrate BioCatch and a11y, create resolvers on BFF, write queries or mutations with Apollo, and Spike and implement new functions, mentor new members, and present any new feature or new archive to the whole team. Take sharing section, Own some training class in office...

- Team size: 12

- Role: Fullstack-Developer



Software Engineer

FPT Software

Sep 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 4 months)

Health and Care Project

- Team size: 10

- Role: Front-end Developer

During my work, I have won the hackathon with my chatbox which increases the UX/UI and profit

Education



Greenwich University

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology Sep 2018 - Dec 2022

Licenses & Certifications



Graph Developer - Associate - Apollo GraphQL

51793318-c989-4c57-a9f3-ee0c0310144f



Amazon Web Services Cloud Practitioner - Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Skills

React Native • Jira • React • styled-components • GraphQL • Apollo GraphQL • Jenkins • Node.js • GitHub • Sonarqube